Kayleen Barzaga

Graphic Designer

(702) 970-1183 barzaga@unlv.nevada.edu

SUMMARY

Patient and experienced problem solver, with more than 4 years of history in high volume environments. Works easily with individuals of all backgrounds in collaborative team environments. Seeking to support administrative operations with advanced organizational and problem-solving abilities.

SKILLS

- Adobe Indesign
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Time management
- Exceptional communication skills
- Fluently Bilingual (English and Spanish)
- Detailed

EXPERIENCE

Amazon, LAS7 6001 E Tropical Pkwy, Las Vegas, NV 89115 - Warehouse Worker

September 2020 - Now

- Stow products into correct inventory bins
- Waterspider

Aldo, 795 S Grand Central Pkwy #2247, Las Vegas, NV 89106 - Sales Associate

October 2018 - September 2020

- Increased sales by 15% by offering consultation on products and services and applying customer service and upselling techniques.
- Prepared merchandise for sales.
- Developed positive customer relationships through friendly greetings and excellent service.
- Helped customers with questions, problems, and complaints in person and via telephone.
- Maintained up-to-date knowledge of product and service offerings to serve as an informational resource to customers and team members.

LVRE, 3100 W Sahara Ave., Las Vegas, Nevada - Receptionist

Feb. 2016 - Apr. 2017

 Answered an average of 10 calls per day by addressing customer inquiries, solving problems and providing needed information.

- Greets and directs visitors to the company.
- Receives, sorts and forwards incoming mail.
- Coordinates the pickup and delivery of express mail services (FedEx, UPS, etc.)
- Assists in the ordering, receiving, stocking, and distribution of office supplies.

EDUCATION

UNLV, 4505 S Maryland Pkwy, Las Vegas, Nevada - Graphic Design

Aug. 2018 - May 2022

- Senior
- B.S. in Graphic Design.
- Dean's Honors List
- 3.68 GPA

Valley High School, 2839 Burnham Ave, Las Vegas, Nevada

Graduated 2018

- Maintained 4.2 weighted GPA.
- Ranked in top 5% of graduating class.
- Completed over 200 hours of community service with various organizations such as Three Square, Camp Foxtail, Valley High School, Las Vegas Rescue Mission and different marathons.
- I.B. program Junior Class Representative from 2016-2017.
- Participated in Feminist Club for 4 years, and Key Club for 3 years.
- Participated in AP or Honors level coursework since the 9th grade.